"Teitan High School"
This story is about
me, Shinichi Kudo
The story just before
Edogawa Conan became
It's Shinichi Kudo!
This popular cartoonist murder case.
It's amazing to unravel
that extraordinary trick!
Police officer Megure
also praised him.
Of Shinichi Kudo student
"Inspector Megure,
Metropolitan Police Department"
The reasoning that was sharper than usual
With early resolution of this case
I can say that I led
It’s not that great
"Shinichi Kudo"
Because I am a detective.
Besides, if it's Holmes that I adore
Half of the time and effort I spent
I would have solved the case.
then
Mr. Kudo, please.
I'm in a hurry, I'm sorry
- wait!
- Wait a minute...
cool
-So cool!
- cool
-By
e-Bye
Show your panties, Ran.
"Mori Ran"
Shinichi!
Light pink
It's a lie, I didn't see it
So how do you know?
It's a simple reasoning
first
Yesterday was Ran's 17th birthday.
second
A gift from Ran’s
mother who’s separated
Uncle opened it at will
Dad?
Looks like you've been obsessed
with the cafe manager under your house
'This embarrassing
thing is telling Ran'
'What the hell are
you thinking!'  I mean
third
If Ran likes her mother
She's right she's wearing that underwear
Dad must have been
dying about useless things!
Well, don't be so angry
You don’t mean that bad either.
Still very popular
Have help, column
Can I organize myself?
It's cold, isn't it your childhood friend
You are the cold one
You're not giving birthday presents these days.
When I was young, I gave it without forgetting
Sherlock Holmes Dictionary
or Sherlock Holmes...
I don't know
What high school girls want to have
I want to go to the amusement park!
Tropical Land!
Tropical Land?
Why, I told you last time
If I win the karate do competition
To shoot anything
I want to go to tropical land
No, not kid
Wait, wait
Is it a couple fight from the morning?
Don't say weird
Sonoko
Ran says he wants to go
to Tropical Land with him.
I!
I want to go with Sonoko
Come on, Sonoko
I will be late for class
hurry!
Why are you angry?  Ran guy
"Mori detective office"
Okay
Shunsaku's whereabouts
Detective Kogoro
Mori will surely find you.
Please don't worry...
Don't worry, please wait
Please
Please find Shunsaku somehow
This is a picture of the child
Yes
-Please go carefully
.-Thank you for Shunsaku.
What is Shunsaku!
Is this the job of Kogoro Mori?
I can't stand it!
"Yoko Okino"
A guy like me is also true
Isn't it time for Yoko to come out?
Yoko!
Are you shooting a
new drama right now?
Yes, that Okino Yoko
It's your first time
trying to play detective!
Everyone, look!
Yoko is a detective?
Did anyone refer to
your role as a detective?
-Yes
.-Role acting?
-He is an excellent detectiv
e-He is
Detective
-This is Kogoro Mori!
-This is Kudo Shinichi!
I'm really a fan
I definitely want to meet you
Damn, that detective kid.
You always stand out more than me!
It's wet, it's wet!
Make sure nothing is lost
And
The homeroom teacher Tatsumi
was hospitalized longer than expected,
I, a temporary teacher, will
lead the school trip tomorrow.
-Kitajima is leading!
-I'm so nervous!
Anyway, everyone
-Good thing
.-Be aware.
Let's make a fun school
trip with responsible actions
I have to report what
I learned as a group
Take note
Then that’s it
Any questions?
"A challenge to Shinichi Kudo"
It is expected!
Is this your first trip together
since elementary school?
Tomorrow I will go around the museum
Then Lake Ashino!
In the evening free time...
Shinichi, is there a place you want to go?
Shinichi!
I mean
I'm not going on a school trip
Why?
Is a waste of time
The actual case is much
more studied than that.
People or
Everything in the world can be studied
I go
Have fun
Shinichi
"Kudo"
"A challenge to Shinichi Kudo"
It's fun
"Teitan High School 2nd Grade Class B"
- Hello!
-Ran, hello!
Sonoko, what did you pack so much?
Change clothes and cosmetics
Match underwear
Match underwear?
I will definitely make a
boyfriend during my school trip!
Your passion for
dating is so great
What are you talking about like someone
else's job?  You should make it too
That detective otaku
I have no idea where I like it
Because it's pretty popular
That you are the wife on this trip
I gotta let the
stupid girls know
What's up, what is it?
Shinichi is not coming
Why?
Like a school trip was a waste of time
That idiot
Everyone, please pay attention
I will introduce
Who will guide you this time
This is Mr. Nishida
I'm Mai Nishida.
Thank you for 3 days.
It's so pretty!
charisma
-My sister, tell me your phone number!
-I'll start soon
I'll be leaving soon
Wait!
I'm sorry, Mr. Kitajima,
for oversleeping.
Glad it's not too late
-That's great
.-What?
Board the bus in your order
- Yeah!
I want to sit in the front seat this time
what?
On the subject that you said not to come
I changed my mind
Sometimes I play
like kids with boredom
I wanted to not be bad
You are a kid too
What, how is it?  Good
Now the couple can go on
their honeymoon together
Sonoko!
'Challenge to Shinichi Kudo'
'During a school trip'
'I will kidnap
someone in your class'
'Your victory if you keep it to the end'
'If I can't keep it, my victory'
'If I win'
``I have to return the
name'High School Detective'
'This is a one-on-one battle between you and me'
'But, give me a hint'
'The place of kidnapping is on the boat'
'hijacker'
- Awesome!
- Wait a minute!
Look at this
pretty
Shinichi!
welcome
Teitan High School
sophomore B class
This is Captain Azuma.
From now on, I will explain
how to use a lifeboat.
Please gather to the front deck
Hello everyone!
- Hello hello
I'm Minamida. Thank you.
In case of an emergency
Wearing this life jacket
-Evacuate with a lifeboat on the deck
.-Isn't that cool?
-It feels like an adul
t-Then the life jacket
-I chose that man
.-I'll explain how to wear it
-I will definitely make it mine
.-If you put your arm in like this...
This boat will go around
the lake for about an hour.
First, enjoy the scenery around
here to your heart's content.
- Yes Yes
Closed room on the
water for an hour from now
Come anywhere
I will surely protect these guys
Isn't it Shinichi Kudo, a high school detective?
Yeah
I'm a fan, nice to meet you
Mr. Minamida
Does Minamida have a girlfriend?
Sorry
I have a job, sorry!
Wait!
I won't miss
50 minutes remaining
On this cruise ship operating at 20 km/h
Approaching without being noticed from the outside
Almost impossible
If i'm a kidnapper
Will already be on this ship
Captain Azuma Kunio
Sailor Minamida Kyosuke
-I'm sorry I have to go down there
.-Then I'll go too.
Report Kitajima, the temporary homeroom teacher,
Receptionist Mai Nishida
But
by the way...
Even if some of the
four are kidnappers,
Ok?
It won't be possible
to take a student here.
How will it come?
What's going on?
With a scary face
No, it's nothing
I feel good because I'm on the water
-Hey, let's take a picture together
.-What?
In the past, we often filmed together
There aren't any pictures taken these days
Now, cheese!
what is this?
Smile too
Now, once again
Hate!
Sonoko
Nausea
What is it, sea sickness?
Are you okay, Suzuki?  OK?
Sir, don’t stutter
It's more roaring
Sonoko
There's a room to lie down inside
-Kudo, help me
.-Yes.
OK?
Thank you, Mr. Minamida
Huh
You don't even say hello to me?
Motion sickness medicine
I would bring it
It's okay, I have it
here
Thank you, Mr. Mai.
You're welcome, this is my job
Me true
The lady who often
rides the cruiser at home
Don't get seasick
-You have a cruiser at home?
Suzuki is the lady of the
Suzuki conglomerate ever since.
You don’t need to say “Let’s see me like this”
Mr. Minamida
Could you please stay with me?
No i have a job
By Sonoko
We will be there
What, have me too?
Do you?  Then don't overdo it
Be comfortable
I'm gone, Mr. Minamida
Sonoko!
Okay, don't be angry
Because it’s okay to be alone
The two go out
I have to make a little new
and enjoyable memories
Will you really be okay?
You have to be quiet
Go out quickly
Sonoko
Lock the door securely from the inside
Never open it to
anyone other than me
Why should it be?
The unsightly vomiting
Don't you hate to be seen by other people?
yea, I got it
What did you say?
It's nothing, I told
you to stay asleep
"rest area"
Excuse me
I mean the weather
It seems to be quite cloudy in the future
Yes
And one student
I am in the break room due to seasickness
Not severe
is it?  Good job
"rest area"
Everyone, please look here
Can you see it?
Hakone Shrine on Lake Ashino
Created in 757...
Yes, I take it
Done!
- Thank you thank you
-Did you get it right?
- Yeah
30 minutes remaining
What happened?
hijacker
It's still a little weird, Shinichi
Ever since I got on the cruise
it's not like that
I can know
I can tell
What, what did you just make?
-I don't know
.-Let's go first.
Look over there
Sonoko's headband.
Is Sonoko here?
Mr. Minamida
Please tell the captain to
stop the ship right away.
Okay
"Warehouse, common room"
Stay safe, Sonoko
Sonokoga
no!
Suzuki?
What the hell happened here?
I don't know yet
One life jacket here is gone.
life jacket?
After all, Sonoko is on the lake...
It’s still too early
Mr. Kitajima, Mr. Minamida
-Please check the inside of the boat
.-Yes
Captain contacted the police
Please ask me to
investigate the lake shore.
I know
Mr. Mai
He told the kids not to worry
It was locked tightly over there
Was it open while arguing with Sonoko?
Inside is empty
One person can hide here
The kidnapper was hiding
here from the beginning
I hit Sonoko who is alone
Did you put on a life jacket
and jump into the lake together?
The current location is in the
middle south of Lake Ashino.
Yeah
I'll dock right away.
Suzuki!
It just made a loud noise, but rest assured
that there is no problem with the ship.
"Warehouse, no entry"
That way?
no
Let's find another place
"No entry"
"Hakone Pirate Ship Boarding Area"
I was holding the
key in the wheelhouse
I was on the deck in front of the ship
I didn't know this would happen
It's okay, this...
Shinichi
Let's wait inside
Look at that!
Contact the Research Headquarters right now!
The kidnapped
Suzuki's second daughter
Although there is no contact from the criminal yet
Most likely the ransom is the purpose
"Detective Tamagawa,
Kanagawa Police"
Our mission is
To find and protect
Sonoko Suzuki.
What are you!
Shinichi Kudo
I'm a detective
Please let me cooperate with the investigation
Detective?
You know, the press covered
A detective who has solved
several difficult cases in Tokyo.
I don’t know how great you are,
Outsiders are banned from entering here.
I'm not an outsider
Sonoko is a precious classmate
Contact Lieutenant Megure at
the Metropolitan Police Department.
Let me participate in the investigation
I don't play with the Police Department!
What are you doing?
Investigate, investigate!
- Yeah!
Wait
Please tell me one
How much is left in
the oxygen tank found
Why ask that?
No, thank you
"Welcome to Teitan High
School sophomore B class"
Hello, Dad?
What?
The second girl in the
rich family was kidnapped?
I'm so worried
It's your precious friend
I will surely find Sonoko
I'll go right there, so wait!
Hello?  Dad?
Sonoko
Please stay safe
Inspector Megure
The police here refused to
cooperate with the investigation.
Is it like that
Tamagawa of the prefectural police
As much as my 10,000 times
He’s a very inflexible
and knowledgeable man.
Impossible to attack
It is called Everest
of the current police.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you
no
I will do it my own way
"Incoming Call
Caller ID Restriction"
Yeah
Shinichi Kudo?
hijacker?
answer
Sonoko will be okay?
For now
Get it out of here, idiot!
But it was a one-sided game
Even though I gave you that much hint
This is not fun
So tomorrow another one
Go to the reception
Are you too pathetic
I could give you a
bigger hint this time
What?
Tomorrow the kidnapping will be carried out at noon.
Without a second mistake
Until then
Revealing your identity
I will save Sonoko
Ran
I told you to wait at the hotel.
You are the same
I knew you were here
I thought you would
definitely move for Sonoko.
The only place I can think of was here
Now, this
Didn't you keep eating anything?
When you get into the case,
you forget everything else.
Thanks
Let me help too
Even if you're there, it doesn't help
I want to do something for Sonoko
Sonoko is my friend
If I was in the same situation
Sonoko would have been restless too
Me true
Since before, you won't
hear once you speak
Did you find something?
If really here
Even if there was a criminal's footprint
It must have been erased by the rain
"What if"?
The killer brought Sonoko here
You came up to the ground
right
Men's wet suit and
The life jacket disappeared
from the ship was found here.
nevertheless
If that's the killer's trick...
What do you mean?
The amount of oxygen
left in the oxygen tank.
Here is where Sonoko might have been missing
And the place where the oxygen tank was found is here
Even if you swim in a straight line
Too much oxygen left
The killer left the evidence here in advance
I was trying to make them think that
the kidnapping was done by an outsider.
Then the killer
You mean you were on board at that time?
I do not know
Anyway, I have no choice but to
check the cruise ship once more.
Ran
Huh
Let's examine the case again
When you hear the sound of drowning
All gathered on the deck in front of the ship
Captain Azuma
was holding the key
Also
It's impossible for anyone
on the ship to kidnap Sonoko.
For sure
Someone must have
kidnapped Sonoko while hiding.
no
The four charges
It hasn't been fully resolved yet
I can trick you into
making an alibi.
Gunpowder trail
As expected
gunpowder?
For example here
Tie heavy loads with ropes
and tie them up in advance
And install a small fire device
Burning the rope and breaking it
As Jim falls into the lake
It can make you mistake
it like someone is missing
In other words
Kidnapping Sonoko
Before I could hear the sound of drowning
So where is Sonoko?
It wasn't on board!
Drowned in a lake by a criminal
Are you saying it's not
being found in that state?
Ran
OK
Sonoko was safe
Were you okay?
What do you mean?
Shinichi!
I'll explain
The challenge came to me
The sender is the kidnapper
On a boat on a school trip
It was a challenge to kidnap
some of my classmates.
And a while ago
I got a call from him
about the second offense.
At noon tomorrow
He said he'd kidnap one more.
When the call came, I
heard Sonoko's voice.
What is
why?
Why didn't you call the police
when the challenge came?
The case is not like a game
It's not a detective's job to
endanger the surroundings!
I don't think it's a game
This
It's a confrontation between me and that guy
Battle?
With such a cowardly person
-What does it mean to confront?
-It has meaning!
Because he's a cowardly criminal
If I run away from the confrontation
Maybe next time they
come in a more mean way
Written on the challenge
Breaking the call for a
one-on-one confrontation
More so
Besides...
Besides, what?
no
never mind
Anyway, now we have to
stop the killer's next crime.
And I'll catch the guy
who will appear there
The only way
Trust me sometimes, Ran
I'll believe
But instead
Don't keep it a secret to everyone
Ok
I will do what you say
"Prince Hotel"
As you know
Today at noon, 12 o'clock
There was a second crime notice.
As a result of the current police
consultation with the school on this issue,
Rather than go back to Tokyo
Staying at this hotel
at the time of the crime
Concluded that it was safe
Are you okay?
At noon
Everyone gathers in this main hall.
All five doors are
locked from the inside
Make it closed
So the kidnapper
I can't even approach you.
great
And!
Police officers are placed outside every door.
together
There are police officers
at all entrances of this hotel.
In other words, you
It is protected by a triple wall.
I hope we reach noon with confidence
If it's a wall, there's one more!
You idiot, put this one!
-Da
d-Uncle
What, you!
You've been waiting for a long time
My name is
Detective Kogoro Mori.
He is also the father
of Ran over there.
Another detective
I will be more than happy to
cooperate with this investigation.
General parents, please do
not intervene in the investigation
-So I'm a detective..
.-Everyone!
Go back to each room
When you're ready, gather
in the main hall and wait.
-Ove
r-Over!
Hey, wait!  Wait, hey!
Dad, you really are here
Of course
Can you stay still
in your company?
That detective, I am not allowed
to cooperate with investigation
You won't be able to
Pretending to be on the subject of the police
I'll keep everyone here at noon
Uncle take care outside the hotel
Do not disturb the guards
Yes
What are you telling me to do?
Dad, take care of the outside
For Sonoko.
I know
Then ask me inside, detective kid.
Yes, don't make a mistake either
You this child, do it in moderation
Okay, shall we look
back and come first?
First of all, I will
check this main hall
Ran, you're resting in the room
You haven't slept almost since last night.
Huh
Sonoko
Shinichi will catch the killer soon.
Keep up until then
What?
-Fukud
a-Yes
-Miyosh
i-Yes
-Morimot
o-Yes
Yes, I like it
All the students gathered above
This is the basement
There are only five entrances.
All locked from the inside
There is a policeman outside the door.
And
Detective Tamagawa is the
only one with the master key.
Vents are so small that it is
impossible for people to pass.
This is the perfect backroom
Now, where will it come from
"Kanagawa Prefecture Police"
This is detective Kogoro Mori.
The guard outside the
detective's pet is sure.
In this state, no
rats can enter.
Here too
Whenever something
happens, then...
Please column
Damn it
The day will come to say this
I know, uncle
In this
There is only one person to watch out for
Wait, everyone want to get together?
-Sir, I'm scared
.-It's okay.
-Only 5 minutes left
.-Relax.
at ease
Everyone will be fine,
nothing will happen
The culprit cannot be concluded as a man.
She may be a woman
Possibly the elderly
Make sure to report the
behavior of even one child.
Excuse me
Are you an official?
My name is Detective Kogoro Mori
This is Mai Nishida
She was the guide
on a school trip,
At that time, there was a case
where Suzuki Sonoko was kidnapped.
So I’m worried
Mr. Azuma, Mr. Minamida
Like me, who was on the same
boat at the time of the incident
Captain Azuma
and sailor Minamida.
This is detective Mori.
I'm an excellent detective.
I can't calm down
In case something else will happen
It's okay
In there
There is one more
cheeky detective.
Let's all shoulder to shoulder
-Never let go
.-I'm scared.
Don't everyone worry, it's okay
There are no specifics in
the hallway of the main hall
-It's scary
.-Calm down, it'll be okay.
Do not worry about it
I'll make sure nothing happens
Huh
But
Thinking about what
happened to Sonoko now
I'm nervous
What to think about now
Winning the second crime notice
Just that
Right?
Soon noon
Don't all get out of your seat!
Next 45 seconds
Kidnapper guy
Come anywhere!
This Mori Kogoro will arrest you.
Excuse me. I'll go
to the bathroom.
I also have an urgent phone
call, so I'll just make one call.
What is at this important moment?
It's okay, everyone calm down!
I can't see anything
because of a power outage
What, a power outage?
What happened?
-Recover, recover immediately!
-This guy!
Protect all of you
Would it be okay?
-Finally turned on!
-Are you all okay?
thank God!
Ran
Ran!
Where is Ran?
Are you suspicious of me now?
I've been with these two all the time
We were scared, so we
kept holding your hand
I also
All the doors are locked
What happened?
Ran
Ran!
What is the situation?  Report the situation!
Sorry
What?  One student disappeared?
what?  What's up?
There is still insufficient information, so in detail...
Mister!
What happened?
They said they disappeared,
but the room was a closed room
So how did she take that girl?
What did the police do?
So who was the kidnapped?
Mister
Ran is gone
what?
Shinichi!
This child!
You said you asked for Ran!
I said so!
-What are you doing!
- calm down!
Let go, let go!
Did you take Ran well?
Again my victory
Even if you make the police on your side
You can't protect your friends.
Such a nasty game
It’s not fun even if I keep going
This is the last
In the place where the two were confined
Installed bomb
The bombing time is today midnight
Will you ever be able to find it?
Next 12 hours
Mister
I was sorry earlier
By hitting it as hard as you can
no
I'm grateful
I can't beat me hard
But what happened to this case?
Making a person
disappear so easily
Is the killer a superpower?
Just human
Human with deep darkness in the heart
I got another call from him
To Ran and Sonoko
They installed bombs.
The time limit is
Midnight
what?
I have to find it somehow
nevertheless
Neither how it disappeared
nor the killer knows
How do you find Ran and Sonoko?
No clue
What the police found
It's just a strange
red ink on that handle.
Red ink?
After the electricity is turned on
That door is the door
I went out to find Ran.
There was no ink on
the handle at that time
Then after you go
Are you saying someone
touched it and buried it?
If so, it won't be a clue
Everything is blocked.
no
If it's a clue...
Is there something?
that...
Mr. Minamida and Mr. Mai
I'm sick of what
some of the two said
What?  Even if I die, I have to remember
-One student disappeared?
-She said she was gone
Was the room a closed room?
So how did she take that girl?
What did the police do?
Damn it, what is it?
What does it take?
At least, Mai's crime is
absolutely impossible.
why?
Because Mr. Mai
has been by my side
continue?
Must be?
A suspicious person
With that captain named Azmar
It's a guy named Minamida
What is the basis?
That guy named Minamida
Just before the power outage
Went somewhere to call
Captain Azuma
I went to the bathroom and didn't come back!
I've decided
The kidnapper is Azmada
He must have kidnapped Sonoko.
nevertheless
On the cruise ship, Mr. Azuma
kept holding the helm
Young, still young
Autopilot
Azuma, who made an alibi by
driving a boat with a machine,
He kidnapped Sonoko in the meantime.
So how did you kidnap Ran?
You'll know that by
arresting the killer.
No time, let's go!
"Azuma"
Attack
surely...
'I am the kidnapper'
Again, this guy was the culprit!
damn
When this guy dies
You don't know where
Ran and Sonoko are.
What are you blanking out?
Help quickly!
I care
The arrow on the
back of the will.
It's darkened, but it
looks like it's used in blood
A wound like this...
Mister
This man is not the culprit
what?
He was killed by the real killer.
Sonoko, wake up!
Sonoko!
Ran!
Let's run away
anybody there?
Help me!
Looks like there's no other door?
The windows are only on the ceiling
How are we going?
OK
Shinichi will surely find us
Actually, I was envious
You and Shinichi
I always fight but
still
To be able to believe in this situation
cool
Is it a bomb?
Are we dying?
It's dangerous, Ran
Not a clue
I think I still have time
At least once
I wanted to die after
having a hot relationship
What weak sound are you talking about?
You can do whatever you want from now on
Don't give up
But now you can't
hurt
Don't do that, Ran
Keep going
You'll never see
Ran's round kick again.
If you don’t use it at this time
Why would you do karate?
Ran
Shinichi Ramen
I will never give
up until the end
I won't give up!
Ran, now that's it
stop
Ran!
Maybe the bones are cracked
"Maybe I've gone"
What are you saying so cutely?
Sonoko, let's go outside quickly
No
why?
What do we do?
With this bridge
I can't go down
Sonoko, run away
Please tell Shinichi this place
I can't
Can't go down
Besides, I can't leave you behind
If you're here,
you might both die!
Ran!
must
I'll bring Shinichi
wait
Now Sonoko can live
I'm sorry, Ran
Quickly research around Azuma
Find where Ran and
Sonoko are confined!
There are bombs installed!
I'm doing it!
by the way
You seem to have touched this and
that at will, but you didn't take anything?
of course
Since then, preservation of the former detective
site is a strict rule of investigation!
what?
What's wrong?
No, not really
The detective
What are you going to do with the will?
Inspector Megure
I have something to ask you to investigate.
This room is the most suspicious
"Warehouse, no entry"
Also
I also found out the trick
to kidnap Sonoko with this.
Must be
That's the culprit
But how?
What the police found
It's just a strange
red ink on that handle.
Ink on the handle
Why in my hand?
Sonoko is my friend
If I was in the same situation
Sonoko would have been restless too
surely
But if that's the case, it explains
Megureda
"Megure Jujo"
I found out what was asked
Yeah
Okay
Thank you
And one more
Kudo
I trust you
I'm counting on you
Is there an hour left?
damn
Yes
Mister?  It's me
Where and what are you doing?
I found a clue where Ran is.
- What are you saying?
-I'll explain later
There are five places where there
is a high likelihood of a column.
I have to divide and find
Yes, i see
Wait a second!
Are you still there?
I found a clue to the place of confinement.
Check it out here
We will do it our way
I don’t get directions from anyone
Especially!
As for the detective's instructions.
what?
I'll show you
Organization and status
The detective soul.
Ran
Ran!
Ran, Sonoko!
It is you
Mai Nishida
It's a coincidence
What are you doing in a place like this?
Are you here to check?
The bombs you have
installed are working
What the hell do
you mean a bomb?
Don't be pretentious
Return Ran and Sonoko.
I've been talking politely
As if I was the culprit
I keep getting sick
Immediately after the second kidnapping
Those words you said
So how did you take the girl?
then
How did you know that the
missing person was a girl?
Even the police still knew
nothing but uncertain information.
It doesn't mean much
No, there is
Because you are the culprit.
Then explain
I
How they kidnapped the two
Yes, I like it
First kidnapping
You hang your luggage on the
back deck of the ship in advance
When time passes, it catches
fire and the rope breaks
I set up a device to let the luggage fall
And
To make it look like an outsider's offense
I made a trace of
people hiding indoors
To mislead Sonoko that
he was dragged to the lake.
I stole a life jacket.
Besides
Men's wetsuit and oxygen tank on the lake shore
I put the life jacket
I stole and I'm ready
And
The day of the incident
To Sonoko, who is seasick
You tricked you into being a motion
sickness medicine and fed you sleeping pills
Enter the room with the
spare key you made in advance
Sonoko, who was asleep,
was hidden in some place.
You
Just take your headband
With installed device
The moment everyone was
distracted by the sound of drowning
Dropped into the lake
Look over there
Sonoko's headband.
So
Sonoko misunderstood that
he fell into the lake at that time.
Wait for a moment
Since then, you've been looking
for everything inside the boat.
Still, Mr. Sonoko was nowhere
She wasn't without
She just couldn't find
Because of a simple trick.
Trickery?
It's a mirror
Then Sonoko
She was in the closet in the room next door
"Warehouse, no entry"
It's a technique often used in magic.
Leave the mirror and use the reflection
That makes you think
there's nothing inside
Rudimentary trick
After the police left the cruise ship